Resume

Mitul Shalehin

M.Sc. in IT & B.Sc. in CSE

Tel: 01921186894

E-Mail: mitulshalehin@gmail.com

Address: 64/18, Block-C, Mojidpur, Savar, Dhaka



CAREER SUMMERY

Currently working as an Assistant Database Programmer, IT at Golden Harvest InfoTech. Ongoing M.Sc. in Information Technology from Jahangirnagar University and graduated B.Sc. in Computer Science and Engineering from North South University. Who is Specializes in database management, MySQL, Store Procedure, Software quality assurance, .Net C#(Web), Data analyst. With those experiences, I have a deep understanding of data architecture, data integration, data analyst and SQA. Those are allowed me to efficiently extract, manipulate, and problem solving ability.

Working Experience

* **Year:** June 01, 2022 – Present

Assistant Database Programmer, IT Golden Harvest InfoTech, Mohakhali, Dhaka

Job Responsibilities are:

- Create 200+ database as per project/client requirement.
- Upload, Trigger database and backup the company database.
- Create store procedure, functions query, SSAS and SSIS
- Setup & maintain database server, SQL windows.
- Database performance tuning and query optimization
- Fix data from database if company need.
- Provide informed feedback for database design.
- Write test case and test complex SQL of database & project.
- Provide security & Quality ensure of database & of database
- Data analysis of company from database.

* **Year:** February 2022 – May 2022

Internship/Trainee Developer

Front-X Solution, Framgate, Dhaka

Job Responsibilities are:

- Work with WordPress, Dot Net, Dart projects.
- Develop and fix problems the interface of application.
- UAT, UIT, ULT, End-End Test.
- Build and test database of software firebase & SQL.
- Update the application as customer requirement.
- Check quality assurance of software.

- Update to team if there any problem found.
- Project management and data analysis of project.
- Create user manual, test case report of software.

EDUCATION

* Year: October, 2022 – Present -

Master of Science - IT

Jahangirnagar University, Savar, Dhaka

CGPA: On going

* Year: 2018- 2021

Bachelor of Science – CSE

North South University, Dhaka

CGPA: 3.12 out of 4.00

Project:

• Create big database for junior design project.

- AmaderShop website & mobile application in C# Flutter.
- Developed WordPress project for junior design project.
- Human face & voice detection Ml.

* Passing Year: 2017

Higher Secondary Certificate – Science

Savar College, Savar, Dhaka

GPA: 3.75 out of 5.00

Membership:

• Ex- SEO- Student Event Organizer Organized Sports Day, Cultural day, farewell

* Passing Year: 2015

Secondary School Certificate – Science

Chapain New Model High School, Savar, Dhaka

GPA: 4.67 out of 5.00

Membership:

• Ex SQCC- Student's Quality Control Circle

Program Languages SKILLS

1.C# (Dot Net), Python, Machine Learning, Flutter.

2. Database: MySQL, Oracle Database, Firebase Database

EXTRA SKILLS

- 1. Database: Microsoft SQL, MySQL Workbench, PostgreSQL, InterBase SQL
- 2. Numerical Analysis: MATLAB.
- 3. SQA: Selenium & Test Studio.
- 3. Data Analysis: Python, MS Excel, MS Power BI.
- 4. Microsoft Office Package: Excel, Excess.
- 5. Computer Software Skills and Expert at using Internet.

INTERESTS

- 1. Data Analysis.
- 2. Database Management.
- 3. Software Quality Assurance.
- 3. Machine Learning Program Languages.
- 4. Networking, Web Technology and Telecommunication.
- 5. Being involved with charities.

Personal Information

Name : Mitul Shalehin Father Name : Md. Shahidul Islam

Mother Name : Nasima Islam

Permanent Address : 64/18, Block-C, Mojidpur, Savar, Dhaka

Date of Birth : 10 August, 1999

Religion : Islam

Contact : 01921186894

E-mail : mitulshalehin@gmail.com

GitHub Username : https://github.com/mitul-shalehin (For Project)
Linkedin : linkedin.com/in/mitul-shalehin-53949b194/

REFRRENCE

1. Umme Honey

Officer - HR \mid Golden Harvest InfoTech

Cell: +8801313082594

Email: umme.it@goldenharvestbd.com

2. MD. Shahriar Hussain

Lecturer | Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering

North South University

Phone: +880255668200 Ext: 6375

Email: shahriar.hussain01@northsouth.edu

The information mentioned above is true to the best of my belief, and I take full responsibility for any correctness of the information.

Name: Mitul Shalehin

[Signature]